capetown-direct.com 2013-03-29

# Privacy Policy

**Popular regions:**

 **Accommodation types:**

Close

**Privacy Policy**

_www.capetown-direct.com_ is serious about protecting the privacy of our owners and accommodation seekers. We use information collected about you only to process and bill orders and to make our Website a more useful and valuable service. We respect the privacy of those who visit or become advertisers. Our privacy policy is stated below, but please be aware that should you follow a link on our website to another website, you are no longer covered by this policy. It's a good idea to understand the privacy policy of any website before sharing personal information with it.

**Your Information: What, How, and Why?**

**Property Owners/Advertisers and Vacation Planning Visitors**

In order to process a request you may have of us we need to know contact information that could include all or some of the following: your full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of an advertising listing, a method of payment. www.capetown-direct.com will use this information to contact you from time to time with critical customer updates and information, or to send you information about new services or opportunities. You will be able to "opt out" and not receive marketing information, but we must always be able to email you critical information about your account and our mutual business relationship.

**Enquiries**

Accommodation seekers may send enquiries to our property owners/advertisers through a property's booking enquiry form on www.capetown-direct.com. If you choose to send an enquiry through these links, your personal information, including your email address and any other information you supply, will be visible to the owner of the property you enquired about so that they might reply directly to you. Do not share information in the email that you are not prepared to allow them to have, including, but not limited to, credit card and bank account information. These enquiries are sent to both the individual owner/advertiser you selected and retained by www.capetown-direct.com. The resulting enquiry is available for review only by the owner/advertiser to whom they were initially addressed and to www.capetown-direct.com customer service employees, who may be asked by advertisers for their past enquiry information.

All enquiries sent through www.capetown-direct.com are accepted and are governed by our Terms and Conditions of Service and our Privacy Policy.

**How Do We Protect Your Information Once We Have It?**

All personal information is stored in a database on a secure server. We do not store credit card numbers or identifying information on any www.capetown-direct.com server.

**What is a Cookie and Why Do We Use Them?**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to store in a Web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. www.capetown-direct.com may use cookies to store some personal preferences for your future visits. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly; therefore, your time spent on our site can be more personalized and productive. You'll find that cookies are an industry standard and are used at most major Websites in much the same way we use them here at www.capetown-direct.com.

By using our Website and signing up for www.capetown-direct.com services, you consent to the collection and use of the previously mentioned information by www.capetown-direct.com and our affiliates. This policy is subject to change without notice. Privacy issues represent a growing concern for all Web users. To keep up-to-date with our policies, please check this page frequently. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.
